<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="concerts.xsl" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="homepage.xsl" ?>
<concerts xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="concerts.xsd">
	<concert cID="CT001">
		<event-name>LR Live</event-name>
		<artist>VIXX LR</artist>
		<genre>K-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>09:00:00</end>
		<organizer>SAMAT FOUNDATION</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Kakao Talk</promoter>
			<promoter>Universal Music Studios</promoter>
			<promoter>HitzFM</promoter>
			<promoter>JellyFish</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		VIXX LR (Korean: 빅스 LR) is the first official sub-unit of South Korean boy group VIXX formed by Jellyfish Entertainment. 
		Established in August 2015, VIXX LR consists of VIXX's main vocalist Leo and main rapper Ravi. 
		The sub-unit debuted with their first mini album, titled Beautiful Liar and will performing LIVE for us FANATICS! EXCITED MUCH?!
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT002">
		<event-name>BTS World Tour: Love Yourself</event-name>
		<artist>BTS</artist>
		<genre>K-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>09:00:00</end>
		<organizer>ARMY Corps</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Kakao Talk</promoter>
			<promoter>BigHit</promoter>
			<promoter>Jongkook Merons</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		BTS World Tour: Love Yourself is the third worldwide concert tour headlined by South Korean band BTS to promote their Love Yourself series, 
		including their Love Yourself: Her EP, Love Yourself: Tear studio album, and Love Yourself. Come on ARMYs WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT003">
		<event-name>SVT Ideal CUT</event-name>
		<artist>SEVENTEEN</artist>
		<genre>K-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>09:00:00</end>
		<organizer>CARAT BONG BONG</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>CARATZ</promoter>
			<promoter>Pledis</promoter>
			<promoter>Mosh Mosh Tv</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		The 13 talented and good looking boys from SEVENTEEN will be having their concert in several countries, greeting 
		their fans from the world.Since then, they have been actively promoting and came up with many of their hit songs such as ‘Mansae’, 
		‘Very Nice’, ‘Boom Boom’, ‘Clap’ and so on! Lets get your CARAT BONG CLAPPING!
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT004">
		<event-name>Jay Chou's Magical Live</event-name>
		<artist>Jay Chou (周杰倫)</artist>
		<genre>C-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>10:00:00</end>
		<organizer>Chair Corps</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>GO XUAN</promoter>
			<promoter>MyFM</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		Jay Chou's First ever magical live! Many Surprises await at this mysterious new concert! 
		Special secret guests stars also await you at this concert! As any die-hard fan will already know, 
		Jay Chou tickets are hard to come by because the star has kept fans waiting for his latest tour. 
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT005">
		<event-name>AMeiZING World Tour</event-name>
		<artist>Zhang Hui Mei (张惠妹)</artist>
		<genre>C-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>10:00:00</end>
		<organizer>AMeiZING</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>MyFM</promoter>
			<promoter>Meiri Jin</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		A-Mei Is DA BOMB! She has been in the music industry for more than 16 years and she has even been nicknamed as the 
		“Pride of Taiwan” and “Taiwanese Madonna”. A-Mei is one artist that can really entertain you with her singing, dancing and showmanship. 
		This firecracker is now in the middle of her AMeiZING World Tour and guess where she’s heading to? Yes, she’s making a stop here at Fanatics for show!
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT006">
		<event-name>A Classic Tour</event-name>
		<artist>Jacky Cheung (周杰倫)</artist>
		<genre>C-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>10:00:00</end>
		<organizer>Star Planet</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Goldsands</promoter>
			<promoter>MyFM</promoter>
			<promoter>Allianz</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		The legendary “God of Song” Jacky Cheung will return to perform for a night performance for us FANATICS.
		Jacky Cheung “A Classic Tour” was first brought into Malaysia in last January with ticket demand far exceeding supply. 
		And this upcoming “Encore” tour is anticipated to be another sellout concert! 
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT007">
		<event-name>Fly FlaMANGOES</event-name>
		<artist>Kenshi Yonezu (米津 玄師)</artist>
		<genre>J-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>07:00:00</start>
		<end>10:00:00</end>
		<organizer>Lemon Corps</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>SmaRT fLY</promoter>
			<promoter>Meiji</promoter>
			<promoter>BNHA</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		Yonezu continues to be praised across Japan, and it’s been shown that he enjoys success with people in their teens all the way into their 50s. 
		Thriving in this success, Yonezu embarked on a tour around the country.Kenshi Yonezu will perform his best new song titled 'Lemon' which was written as the main 
		theme song for the TBS Friday drama “Unnatural”.
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT008">
		<event-name>Paper Bunnies</event-name>
		<artist>Kumabukuro and Rabbit</artist>
		<genre>J-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>22:00:00</start>
		<end>23:00:00</end>
		<organizer>SAMAT FOUNDATION</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Meiji</promoter>
			<promoter>oDYSSEY</promoter>
			<promoter>SMART</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		The first ever Paper Bunnies Live is coming soon! Many wonders await at the first appearance of this fantastic BEAST DUOS!
		Watch them live as they perform BULGOGI one of the craziest solo that makes their fans waiting for more!!!
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT009">
		<event-name>Tokyo Fantasy</event-name>
		<artist>SEKAI NO OWARI</artist>
		<genre>J-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>22:00:00</start>
		<end>23:00:00</end>
		<organizer>Dragon Heart</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Knights</promoter>
			<promoter>Sekai no Baka</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		End of the World (SEKAI NO OWARI) is currently one of Japan’s most popular and skilled creative groups. The group is comprised of four distinctly 
		talented members: Nakajin, Fukase, Saori and the masked clown DJ LOVE. These four childhood friends grew closer while collectively managing the 
		live music venue clubEARTH, which they built from the ground up. 
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT010">
		<event-name>The Pray for the Wicked Tour</event-name>
		<artist>Panic! At The Disco</artist>
		<genre>E-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>22:00:00</start>
		<end>23:00:00</end>
		<organizer>Monalisa Ballad</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>HitzFM</promoter>
			<promoter>oDYSSEY</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		Make sure you see Panic! At the Disco live, and prepare for an experience that will last for a lifetime!
		One of the biggest acts to emerge out of the emo movement of the mid-2000s, Panic! At the Disco transcended their early fame, 
		transforming into a vehicle for singer Brendon Urie's charismatic, cross-pollinated brand of pop
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT011">
		<event-name>Take my Love Away Tour</event-name>
		<artist>Bad Suns</artist>
		<genre>E-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>22:00:00</start>
		<end>23:00:00</end>
		<organizer>SALT CORP</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Meiji</promoter>
			<promoter>oDYSSEY</promoter>
			<promoter>SMART</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		After a thunderous two years following the release of their first EP, Transpose, and their debut, Language and 
		Perspective, Bad Suns’ newest effort, Disappear Here, aims to quell all concerns of a sophomore slump in the form of 
		their most dynamic and introspective work yet. Having to follow monumental singles from their debut, 
		like “Cardiac Arrest” and “Salt”, Bad Suns gave themselves quite the mountain to climb.Fortunately, much of Disappear Here  rises to the challenge.
		</description>
	</concert>
	
	<concert cID="CT012">
		<event-name>Meet you There</event-name>
		<artist>5SOS</artist>
		<genre>E-POP</genre>
		<date>2019-01-19</date>
		<start>22:00:00</start>
		<end>23:00:00</end>
		<organizer>WHOTMATE corp</organizer>
		<promoters>
			<promoter>Kangaroos</promoter>
			<promoter>NoSpidersPLS Corps</promoter>
		</promoters>
		<description>
		Being an enormous fan of 5 Seconds of Summer for a consecutive five years now, I think that 
		I have gained the right to do a review on their well-known Meet You There tour. After a two year break in 
		which the 5SOS guys took well-needed time for themselves and began working on their third album Youngblood, Luke Hemmings, 
		Ashton Irwin, Michael Clifford and Calum Hood returned in full force with countless hit songs and a worldwide tour that managed to sell out within minutes in various locations.
		</description>
	</concert>
	
</concerts>